blogclarity.com 2014-01-11

# Privacy Policy and Disclosure

**Affiliate Marketing**

I participate in affiliate marketing programs where I receive a small commission when products are purchased through links on my blog. I appreciate when you click on those links because they help support me so I can keep writing Momcomm.

**What information does Momcomm collect?**  
Momcomm collects information from you when you subscribe to the email list or fill out a form. That’s it.

**Does Momcomm use cookies?**

****Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. The cookies are only used for the affiliate links. I don’t see them OR eat them.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

****Because Momcomm values your privacy I’ve taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. Momcomm therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

****Momcomm is in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), and does not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. This website and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

****This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

****If I decide to change the privacy policy, I’ll post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on June 27, 2011.

**Contacting Us**

****If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact me using the information below.

Privacy Policy Created by [Free Privacy Policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/) (with a little tweaking by Melissa)
